

MIGUEL AMARO

Date of birth: 1999-09-30 | Nationaly: Portuguese

Address: Rua das Tipuanas Lt 22, 2925-324 Brejos de Azeitão, Portugal

Tel: +351 936510569 | E-mail: miguelpiresamaro@gmail.com Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/miguel-amaro

PERSONAL PROFILE

Finalizing a degree in Computer Engineering. Regarding work experience, completed a twelve-month internship in the field of helpdesk and general IT support/development and also been acting as a freelance on the Fiverr platform. Currently looking forward to opportunities to be part of projects while planning to do a Master in computer engineering for solidifying my skills and helping me to go further.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Fiverr | Jan 2020 - present

Main performed tasks and learnings: I have been acting as a freelance on the Fiverr platform for developing WEB and mobile applications. With that I have acquired experience in managing different technologies and programming languages.

IT support

Multitipo Artes Gráficas LDA | Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

Main performed tasks and learnings: Internship in the field of IT support in a medium size local company in the area of graphic arts. I learned tools and methods for performing an adequate computer support, designed a maintenance schedule for each computer/laptop and respective peripherical allowing for continuously high performance. I have also developed software/programs to automate some of the monthly processes which improved efficiency across the operation.

EDUCATION

Universidade Europeia

Degree in Computer Engineering | Sep 2018 - Jun 2021

Average (to date): 14/20

SKILLS & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Languages

Portuguese(native); English(intermediary)

Courses & Certificates

CS50 Introduction to computer science; Learn SQL; Web development; Learn Javascript; Marketing Digital; Learn HTML; Learn Python

ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

Federated in Tennis

(From 2005 - Now)

I have been playing tennis since I was five years old, practicing 5 to 10 hours a week and participating in national and international tournaments. I have been able to develop my skills of self-discipline, persistence, time management and networking.

Electoral table member

(Oct 2019)

I was part of an electoral table for the election of members of Parliament in 2019 in the village where I live, Brejos de Azeitão.

Volunteering at "Banco Alimentar"

(June 2019 - Aug 2019)

During the summer holidays I volunteered at the institution "Banco Alimentar" in the Palmela warehouse. This experience taught me the importance of being available to help those in need, to be able to do any kind of work and develop a team spirit and solidarity.